<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rémi Vezy on Rémi Vezy</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rémi Vezy on Rémi Vezy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>CoffeeFlux</title>
      <link>/project/coffeeflux/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/coffeeflux/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DynACof</title>
      <link>/models/dynacof/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/models/dynacof/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The DynACof process-based model computes plot-scale Net Primary Productivity, carbon allocation, growth, yield, energy, and water balance of coffee plantations according to management, while accounting for spatial effects using metamodels from the 3D process-based MAESPA. The model also uses coffee bud and fruit cohorts for reproductive development to better represent fruit carbon demand distribution along the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;infos&#34;&gt;Infos&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Informations about installation, version release, source code and news are available on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/VEZY/DynACof&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;GitHub repository&lt;/a&gt;. This source is always the most up-to-date.
Informations about model description (equations, state of the art, history) can be found on the third chapter of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/323469257_Simulation_de_pratiques_de_gestion_alternatives_pour_l&#39;adaptation_des_plantations_perennes_aux_changements_globaux&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;thesis manuscript&lt;/a&gt; (Vezy, 2017).
NB : the manuscript is partly in French, but this chapter is in English.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;installation&#34;&gt;Installation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The development version from &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt; can be installed with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-r&#34;&gt;# install.packages(&amp;quot;devtools&amp;quot;)
devtools::install_github(&amp;quot;VEZY/DynACof&amp;quot;)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or using the lightweight &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/r-lib/remotes#readme&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;remotes&lt;/a&gt; package:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-r&#34;&gt;# install.packages(&amp;quot;remotes&amp;quot;)
remotes::install_github(&amp;quot;VEZY/DynACof&amp;quot;)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the moment, there is no &lt;a href=&#34;https://CRAN.R-project.org&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CRAN&lt;/a&gt; released version of DynACof, but we work on that. You will soon be able to run this command to install the package:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-r&#34;&gt;install.packages(&amp;quot;DynACof&amp;quot;)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;example&#34;&gt;Example&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a basic example using all defaults (parameters and meteorology) over 2 years :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-r&#34;&gt;rm(list = ls())
library(&amp;quot;DynACof&amp;quot;)
Sys.setenv(TZ=&amp;quot;UTC&amp;quot;)
DynACof(Period= as.POSIXct(c(&amp;quot;1979-01-01&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;1980-12-31&amp;quot;)))
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To use your own data, you&amp;rsquo;ll have to tell DynACof where to find it using &lt;code&gt;Inpath&lt;/code&gt; parameter, and what is the files names with the &lt;code&gt;FileName&lt;/code&gt; parameter list:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-r&#34;&gt;rm(list = ls())
library(&amp;quot;DynACof&amp;quot;)
Sys.setenv(TZ=&amp;quot;UTC&amp;quot;)
DynACof(WriteIt = T, Period= as.POSIXct(c(&amp;quot;1979-01-01&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;1980-12-31&amp;quot;)),Inpath = &amp;quot;1-Input/Aquiares/&amp;quot;,Simulation_Name = &amp;quot;Test1&amp;quot;,FileName = list(Site = &amp;quot;1-Site.R&amp;quot;, Meteo =&amp;quot;2-Meteorology.txt&amp;quot;, Soil = &amp;quot;3-Soil.R&amp;quot;,Coffee = &amp;quot;4-Coffee.R&amp;quot;, Tree = NULL))
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note that the Meteo file can be of any regular format because the model uses the &lt;code&gt;data.table::fread&lt;/code&gt; function internally.
Enjoy !!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;repository-status&#34;&gt;Repository status&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.repostatus.org/#wip&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.repostatus.org/badges/latest/wip.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Project Status: WIP – Initial development is in progress, but there has not yet been a stable, usable release suitable for the public.&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://travis-ci.com/VEZY/DynACof&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://travis-ci.com/VEZY/DynACof.svg?token=oehDDxBpmrzeWX8AdyPo&amp;amp;branch=master&#34; alt=&#34;Travis build status&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://gitter.im/DynACof/Lobby?utm_source=badge&amp;amp;utm_medium=badge&amp;amp;utm_campaign=pr-badge&amp;amp;utm_content=badge&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://badges.gitter.im/DynACof/Lobby.svg?token=1d2e733532f5122f05de&amp;amp;branch=master&#34; alt=&#34;Join the chat at https://gitter.im/DynACof/Lobby\#&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://img.shields.io/badge/License-GPL%20v3-blue.svg&#34; alt=&#34;License: GPL v3&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;acknowledgments&#34;&gt;Acknowledgments&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The DynACof model was mainly developed thanks to the &lt;a href=&#34;../../project/maccac/index.html&#34;&gt;MACCAC project&lt;/a&gt;, which was funded by the french ANR (Agence Nationale de la Recherche). The authors were funded by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cirad.fr/en&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CIRAD&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.inra.fr/en/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;INRA&lt;/a&gt;. The authors are grateful for the support of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.catie.ac.cr/en/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CATIE&lt;/a&gt; for the long-term coffee agroforestry trial, the SOERE F-ORE-T which is supported annually by Ecofor, Allenvi and the French national research infrastructure &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.anaee-france.fr/fr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;ANAEE-F&lt;/a&gt;; the CIRAD-IRD-SAFSE project (France) and the PCP platform of CATIE. CoffeeFlux observatory was supported and managed by CIRAD researchers. We are grateful to the staff from Costa-Rica, in particular Alvaro Barquero, Alejandra Barquero, Jenny Barquero, Alexis Perez, Guillermo Ramirez, Rafael Acuna, Manuel Jara, Alonso Barquero for their technical and field support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;references&#34;&gt;References&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vezy, R., Simulation de pratiques de gestion alternatives pour l’adaptation des plantations pérennes aux changements globaux, in École doctorale science de l&amp;rsquo;environnement, spécialité physique de l&amp;rsquo;environnement. 2017, UNIVERSITÉ DE BORDEAUX: Bordeaux. p. 270. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/323469257_Simulation_de_pratiques_de_gestion_alternatives_pour_l&#39;adaptation_des_plantations_perennes_aux_changements_globaux&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;sub&gt;The DynACof logo was made using &lt;a href=&#34;http://logomakr.com&#34; title=&#34;Logo Makr&#34;&gt;LogoMakr.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EucFlux</title>
      <link>/project/eucflux/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/eucflux/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MACACC project (ANR-13-AGRO-00)</title>
      <link>/project/maccac/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/maccac/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;maccac-project-https-sites-google-com-site-anrmacacc-home&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sites.google.com/site/anrmacacc/home&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;MACCAC Project&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The impacts of Global Changes and the internalisation of the costs of adaptation are expected to be of such a huge economic importance that they recently raised warnings from institutions such as the World Bank (WorldBank, 2012). Just considering the climatic component, the “Tipping-Point” (or emergence of the temperature increase from the current local climatic oscillations) will likely occur within five to ten years under the tropics and just a few decades later for higher latitudes (Mahlstein et al., 2011; Hawkins and Sutton, 2012; IPCC, 2013). The tropics are vulnerable but count with an immemorial experience in the management of low-input agroecosystems under constraints. They offer to the World an invaluable laboratory for testing adaptation scenarios.
Each agroecosystem is defined by a range of temperature and resources beyond which it is no longer viable and should be changed (for crops), or adapted through management practices (for perennial plantations). Some practices can enhance resilience: creating heterogeneity (multi-layers) and diversity (multi-species, several sources of incomes) into the perennial plantations can improve the micro-climate, the effects of facilitation for resource capture (light, water, nutrients), the provision of ecosystem services. Our hypothesis is that some multilayered systems, such as agroforestry, are intrinsically more resilient and could inspire other types of management.
MACCAC gathered economists, stakeholders (Professional Organisations + a large panel of producers, &amp;gt; 300), climatologists, ecophysiologists, modelers, around the question of adaptation of their perennial plantations to global changes. Three perennial plantations were selected as case-studies, owing to their economical importance (woody products and coffee), to their origin (2 tropical, Eucalyptus and Coffee-Agroforestry; one in France, Maritime Pine), and to their structure (mono or multi-layer, main crop in upper or under-storey). In accordance with the stakeholders, few realistic “adaptive management scenarios” that could realistically be implemented in the near future  were studied.
•   These adaptive management scenarios were then investigated by the economists of the project to test the “willingness of adoption” of the stakeholders, using choice experiments that aim in particular at evaluating planters’ preferences for a range of incentive mechanisms (Payments for Ecosystem Services, certifications etc);
•   The climatologists downscaled locally the climatic scenarios for the very next decades and later. These climatic scenarios were then combined with the range of adaptive management scenarios into a biophysical model (&lt;a href=&#34;https://maespa.github.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;MAESPA&lt;/a&gt; + &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/VEZY/DynACof&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;DynACof&lt;/a&gt;) running at the scale of forest and agroforest plots, over full cultural cycles. The model was parameterized and verified according to already existing data from actual field experiments, in a large range of conditions for light (climate and density of shade trees), water (rainfall exclusion experiments), nutrient and CO2 availability (Free Air CO2 Enrichment data). The outputs were of the form of profiles of “ecological resilience” per scenario, including a multi-purpose evaluation of the provision of ecosystem services (yield included), for current and future climates;
•   The “profiles of ecological resilience per scenario” were combined with the “willingness of adoption” and yield finally “a global resilience”, i.e. explicitly including ecological, economical and adoption components of the process of adaptation;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The results on global resilience were then restituted and discussed with stakeholders and ranked according to multi-purpose priorities.The scientific work was evaluated by the stakeholders and the deliverables will be used for outreach, training of planters, students and possibly become tools for decision-building of planters and policy makers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MAESPA</title>
      <link>/models/maespa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/models/maespa/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;brief-history-of-the-model&#34;&gt;Brief history of the model&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maespa is a model of forest canopy radiation absorption, photosynthesis and water balance. The model has a long history, going back to the work of John Norman and Paul Jarvis in the 1970&amp;rsquo;s and 80&amp;rsquo;s. Ying -Ping Wang improved and tested the model for his PhD thesis (then called MAESTRO) (Wang &amp;amp; Jarvis 1990). In 1997 Belinda Medlyn obtained a version of the code from Ying-Ping Wang and revised the model, with the objectives of (i) modularising the code to make the program easier to understand and modify; and (ii) incorporating standard formulations of leaf gas exchange models (see Medlyn 2004 for a full history).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2008, Remko Duursma and Belinda Medlyn started expanding Maestra by including water balance and plant hydraulics routines, largely based on the SPA model by Mat Williams (Duursma and Medlyn 2012). The two models were independent for some time, but since 2013 they use the same code base. The diagram below shows how Maespa incorporates Maestra. It is straightforward to run the model &amp;lsquo;in Maestra mode&amp;rsquo;, which is consistent with the legacy Maestra model.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2018, Vezy et al. (see research article for full author list) modified the model to include several changes relative to the official &lt;a href=&#34;https://bitbucket.org/remkoduursma/maespa/branch/master&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;master&lt;/a&gt; branch of the model:
* voxel-scale leaf evaporation
* Computation of canopy air temperature and vapor pressure.
* Iterations on leaf temperature until convergence
* Aerodynamic conductance computation at plot scale (used for soil + canopy air temperature and vapor pressure)
* Allow two wind extinction profile if ZHT (measurement height) is below canopy height (mainly used in agroforestry with measurements below the shade trees)
* Bug fixes on slope computation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;informations-and-technical-manual&#34;&gt;Informations and Technical manual&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All informations about MAESPA can be found in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://maespa.github.io&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;MAESPA website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Further informations on how to modify the input files to adapt them to the version we developed on the wiki from the unofficial &lt;a href=&#34;https://gitlab.com/VEZY/MAESPA/wikis/home&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Gitlab repository&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://gitlab.com/VEZY/MAESPA&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;exact version&lt;/a&gt; used in Vezy et al. (2018). Carefull, this version is a development version and is not in full agreement with the MAESPA development guidelines (e.g. modified input call for distributed computation). The official, clean, deployed version is the one from repository.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;validation-website&#34;&gt;Validation website&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The results from the validation of the new version of the model are available on this &lt;a href=&#34;https://vezy.github.io/MAESPA_Validation/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;references&#34;&gt;References&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vezy, R., et al., Measuring and modelling energy partitioning in canopies of varying complexity using MAESPA model. Agricultural and Forest Meteorology, 2018. 253-254: p. 203-217. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S016819231830042X&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MAESPA model modification to simulate stands with complex canopies structure</title>
      <link>/publication/vezy_et_al_2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/vezy_et_al_2018/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ReMIX</title>
      <link>/project/remix/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/remix/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STICS</title>
      <link>/models/stics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/models/stics/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simulating the effects of different potassium and water supply regimes on soil water content and water table depth over a rotation of a tropical Eucalyptus grandis plantation</title>
      <link>/publication/christina_et_al_2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/christina_et_al_2018/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simulation de pratiques de gestion alternatives pour l&#39;adaptation des plantations pérennes aux changements globaux</title>
      <link>/publication/vezy_2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/vezy_2017/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Example Talk</title>
      <link>/talk/example-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/example-talk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Embed your slides or video here using &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/post/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;. Further details can easily be added using &lt;em&gt;Markdown&lt;/em&gt; and $\rm \LaTeX$ math code.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spatial analysis of endemism to redefine conservation areas in Western Ghats (India)</title>
      <link>/publication/gaucherel_et_al_2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/gaucherel_et_al_2016/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic: the website designer for Hugo</title>
      <link>/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Academic&lt;/strong&gt; is a framework to help you create a beautiful website quickly. Perfect for personal sites, blogs, or business/project sites. &lt;a href=&#34;https://themes.gohugo.io/theme/academic/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Check out the latest demo&lt;/a&gt; of what you&amp;rsquo;ll get in less than 10 minutes. Then head on over to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Quick Start guide&lt;/a&gt; or take a look at the &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/updates/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Release Notes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/gcushen/hugo-academic/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/gcushen/hugo-academic/master/academic.png&#34; alt=&#34;Screenshot&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key features:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Easily manage various content including homepage, blog posts, publications, talks, and projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensible via &lt;strong&gt;color themes&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;widgets/plugins&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write in &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Markdown&lt;/a&gt; for easy formatting and code highlighting, with &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikibooks.org/wiki/LaTeX/Mathematics&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;LaTeX&lt;/a&gt; for mathematical expressions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social/academic network linking, &lt;a href=&#34;https://analytics.google.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Google Analytics&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://disqus.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Disqus&lt;/a&gt; comments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsive and mobile friendly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Simple and refreshing one page design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multilingual and easy to customize&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;color-themes&#34;&gt;Color Themes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Academic is available in different color themes and font themes.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class=&#34;gallery&#34;&gt;
  
  
  
  
    
  
  &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery-1&#34; data-caption=&#34;Default&#34; href=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/gcushen/hugo-academic/master/images/theme-default.png&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/gcushen/hugo-academic/master/images/theme-default.png&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
  
  
  
  
    
  
  &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery-1&#34; data-caption=&#34;Ocean&#34; href=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/gcushen/hugo-academic/master/images/theme-ocean.png&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/gcushen/hugo-academic/master/images/theme-ocean.png&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
  
  
  
  
    
  
  &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery-1&#34; data-caption=&#34;Dark&#34; href=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/gcushen/hugo-academic/master/images/theme-dark.png&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/gcushen/hugo-academic/master/images/theme-dark.png&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
  
  
  
  
    
  
  &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery-1&#34; data-caption=&#34;Default&#34; href=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/gcushen/hugo-academic/master/images/theme-forest.png&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/gcushen/hugo-academic/master/images/theme-forest.png&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
  
  
  
  
    
  
  &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery-1&#34; data-caption=&#34;Coffee theme with Playfair font&#34; href=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/gcushen/hugo-academic/master/images/theme-coffee-playfair.png&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/gcushen/hugo-academic/master/images/theme-coffee-playfair.png&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
  
  
  
  
    
  
  &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery-1&#34; data-caption=&#34;1950s&#34; href=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/gcushen/hugo-academic/master/images/theme-1950s.png&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/gcushen/hugo-academic/master/images/theme-1950s.png&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
  
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;install&#34;&gt;Install&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can choose from one of the following four methods to install:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;one-click install using your web browser (recommended)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;install on your computer using Git with the Command Prompt/Terminal app&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;install on your computer by downloading the ZIP files&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;install on your computer with RStudio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;quick-install-using-your-web-browser&#34;&gt;Quick install using your web browser&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://app.netlify.com/start/deploy?repository=https://github.com/sourcethemes/academic-kickstart&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Install Academic with Netlify&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Netlify will provide you with a customizable URL to access your new site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On GitHub, go to your newly created &lt;code&gt;academic-kickstart&lt;/code&gt; repository and edit &lt;code&gt;config.toml&lt;/code&gt; to personalize your site. Shortly after saving the file, your site will automatically update&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Read the &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Quick Start Guide&lt;/a&gt; to learn how to add Markdown content. For inspiration, refer to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/gcushen/hugo-academic/tree/master/exampleSite&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Markdown content&lt;/a&gt; which powers the &lt;a href=&#34;https://themes.gohugo.io/theme/academic/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Demo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;install-with-git&#34;&gt;Install with Git&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prerequisites:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://git-scm.com/downloads&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Download and install Git&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/getting-started/installing/#quick-install&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Download and install Hugo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/sourcethemes/academic-kickstart#fork-destination-box&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Fork&lt;/a&gt; the &lt;em&gt;Academic Kickstart&lt;/em&gt; repository and clone your fork with Git:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;git clone https://github.com/sourcethemes/academic-kickstart.git My_Website
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note that if you forked Academic Kickstart, the above command should be edited to clone your fork, i.e. replace &lt;code&gt;sourcethemes&lt;/code&gt; with your GitHub username.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Initialize the theme:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;cd My_Website
git submodule update --init --recursive
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;install-with-zip&#34;&gt;Install with ZIP&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/sourcethemes/academic-kickstart/archive/master.zip&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Download&lt;/a&gt; and extract &lt;em&gt;Academic Kickstart&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/gcushen/hugo-academic/archive/master.zip&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Download&lt;/a&gt; and extract the &lt;em&gt;Academic theme&lt;/em&gt; to the &lt;code&gt;themes/academic/&lt;/code&gt; folder from the above step&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;install-with-rstudio&#34;&gt;Install with RStudio&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/install/#install-with-rstudio&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;View the guide to installing Academic with RStudio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quick-start&#34;&gt;Quick start&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you installed on your computer, view your new website by running the following command:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;hugo server
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now visit &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;localhost:1313&lt;/a&gt; and your new Academic powered website will appear. Otherwise, if using Netlify, they will provide you with your URL.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read the &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Quick Start Guide&lt;/a&gt; to learn how to add Markdown content, customize your site, and deploy it. For inspiration, refer to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/gcushen/hugo-academic/tree/master/exampleSite&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Markdown content&lt;/a&gt; which powers the &lt;a href=&#34;https://themes.gohugo.io/theme/academic/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Demo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Build your site by running the &lt;code&gt;hugo&lt;/code&gt; command. Then &lt;a href=&#34;https://georgecushen.com/create-your-website-with-hugo/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;host it for free using Github Pages&lt;/a&gt; or Netlify (refer to the first installation method). Alternatively, copy the generated &lt;code&gt;public/&lt;/code&gt; directory (by FTP, Rsync, etc.) to your production web server (such as a university&amp;rsquo;s hosting service).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;updating&#34;&gt;Updating&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feel free to &lt;em&gt;star&lt;/em&gt; the project on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/gcushen/hugo-academic/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt; to help keep track of updates and check out the &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/updates&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;release notes&lt;/a&gt; prior to updating your site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before updating the framework, it is recommended to make a backup of your entire website directory (or at least your &lt;code&gt;themes/academic&lt;/code&gt; directory) and record your current version number.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By default, Academic is installed as a Git submodule which can be updated by running the following command:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt;git submodule update --remote --merge
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/update/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Check out the update guide&lt;/a&gt; for full instructions and alternative methods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;feedback-contributing&#34;&gt;Feedback &amp;amp; Contributing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please use the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/gcushen/hugo-academic/issues&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;issue tracker&lt;/a&gt; to let me know about any bugs or feature requests, or alternatively make a pull request.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For support, head over to the &lt;a href=&#34;http://discuss.gohugo.io&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Hugo discussion forum&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;license&#34;&gt;License&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright 2016-present &lt;a href=&#34;https://georgecushen.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;George Cushen&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Released under the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/gcushen/hugo-academic/blob/master/LICENSE.md&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;MIT&lt;/a&gt; license.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div id=&#34;r-markdown&#34; class=&#34;section level1&#34;&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;R Markdown&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see &lt;a href=&#34;http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com&#34; class=&#34;uri&#34;&gt;http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can embed an R code chunk like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&#34;r&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;summary(cars)
##      speed           dist       
##  Min.   : 4.0   Min.   :  2.00  
##  1st Qu.:12.0   1st Qu.: 26.00  
##  Median :15.0   Median : 36.00  
##  Mean   :15.4   Mean   : 42.98  
##  3rd Qu.:19.0   3rd Qu.: 56.00  
##  Max.   :25.0   Max.   :120.00
fit &amp;lt;- lm(dist ~ speed, data = cars)
fit
## 
## Call:
## lm(formula = dist ~ speed, data = cars)
## 
## Coefficients:
## (Intercept)        speed  
##     -17.579        3.932&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;including-plots&#34; class=&#34;section level1&#34;&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Including Plots&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can also embed plots. See Figure &lt;a href=&#34;#fig:pie&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt; for example:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&#34;r&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;par(mar = c(0, 1, 0, 1))
pie(
  c(280, 60, 20),
  c(&amp;#39;Sky&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;Sunny side of pyramid&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;Shady side of pyramid&amp;#39;),
  col = c(&amp;#39;#0292D8&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;#F7EA39&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;#C4B632&amp;#39;),
  init.angle = -50, border = NA
)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;figure&#34;&gt;&lt;span id=&#34;fig:pie&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown_files/figure-html/pie-1.png&#34; alt=&#34;A fancy pie chart.&#34; width=&#34;672&#34; /&gt;
&lt;p class=&#34;caption&#34;&gt;
Figure 1: A fancy pie chart.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
